<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Power Automate on Andrey Paltusov</title>
    <link>http://paltusov.pro/tags/power-automate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Power Automate on Andrey Paltusov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://paltusov.pro/tags/power-automate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics 365 and LinkedIn Power Automate integration</title>
      <link>http://paltusov.pro/2021/11/15/D365-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paltusov.pro/2021/11/15/D365-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Intro  There are several LinkedIn tools in Dynamics 365 - LinkedIn Sales Navigator for Dynamics 365 and LinkedIn Lead Gen integration, but these are rather marketing tools that also require additional costs. What if you just need to enrich your contacts with Linked Profile data? Linked has its own API and it would be nice to use it. In the same time, Power Platform has an integration mechanism and it would be good to use it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Automate Anaplan integration Part 2</title>
      <link>http://paltusov.pro/2021/02/02/anaplan-sharepoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paltusov.pro/2021/02/02/anaplan-sharepoint/</guid>
      <description>Power Automate flow  In this part I will describe file exchange process between Anaplan and SharePoint, built in Microsoft Power Automate. Exporting files from Anaplan consists of several steps:
 Starting the export task Checking the export task is ready Downloading the file  A full description of API methods can be found here. To export files, you need to know the file export code. To get the list of export files, you should call the API method https://api.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Automate Anaplan integration Part 1</title>
      <link>http://paltusov.pro/2021/01/25/anaplan-authentication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paltusov.pro/2021/01/25/anaplan-authentication/</guid>
      <description>Anaplan token  To work with Anaplan, you first need to get an authorization token. Authorization documentation is described here. You can get a token in two ways: by passing a username and password, using certificates. The first method is not very suitable for building integration processes, so I used certificates that can be requested from Anaplan administratorsTo receive a token using a certificate, you need to send a request with parameters to the address https://auth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
